icomuk.co.uk 2019-05-19

# Privacy - Icom UK

Icom (UK) Ltd will use the information provided by you in the course of our dealing with you to process your requests and orders and in order to provide a more personalised web-surfing experience. 

We may also share your information with certain reputable third parties and business partners in order to fulfil your order or request or to obtain professional advice. We would never sell, exchange or pass on your details for commercial gain or reward. If you would like details of who these companies are, please write to Marketing Department, Icom UK Ltd, Blacksole House, The Boulevard, Altira Park, Herne Bay, Kent CT6 6GZ. Please note that we have not and do not share or sell personal information for marketing purposes. 

By providing and submitting any item of personal information you agree to us storing that information. This website also contains various ‘opt-in’ boxes on the relevant pages where you provide your personal information. If you do want us to contact you or provide your personal information to trusted third parties as may be described on the pages of the website, you not should tick the opt-in boxes provided. 

There may be links on our website pages that will transfer you to other websites, where data privacy practices may be different to that of Icom (UK) Ltd. Visitors should consult those other websites’ privacy policies, since we are not responsible for, and have no control over, information that is submitted to or collected by these third parties. Please note that our own micro-sites all comply with our stated policies. 

This privacy policy may be changed by Icom UK Ltd at any time. The revised policy will be posted to this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. Icom UK Ltd will ensure that your personal information is treated with the utmost respect and in accordance with GDPR (General Data Protection Regulations) on the protection of individuals with regard to processing of personal data. 

© ICOM (UK) LTD 2019   
All rights reserved.
